Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - John Dreyfuss, 1998 February; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Dana Thai Soon Burgess, Circa 1998; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Yale Club/Francess Dorn, 1998 February 9; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Versace, 1998 February 12; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - A Conversation with Moms Mabley, 1998 February 22; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Playwrights Series, 1998 February - 1998 March; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Icelandic Evening, 1998 February 26; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Menswear, 1998 March 3; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Book, 1998 March; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Armchair tours of Washington Art, 1998 March; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - A Song of Solomon, 1998 March 8; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - WAF Panel, 1998 March 17; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Peter Fay Cancelled, 1998 March 10; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Andy Warhol Cancelled, 1998 March 12; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hot Mustard Cancelled, 1998 March 24; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - The Screaming Woman, 1998 March 31; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Printmaking Workshop, 1998 March 8; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 1998 Spring Advertising/General Correspondence, Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - April Copy (Calendar), 1998 April; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - May 1998 Calendar, 1998 May; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - June Calendar Copy, 1998 June; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Embassy of Slovenia, 1998 April 1; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Salons of France/Hillwood, 1998 April 2; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Roberto Burle Marx, 1998 April 5; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Olivier Bernier, 1998 April 7; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Embassy Row Walking Tour, 1998 April 9; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Belgium, 1998 April 14; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Robert Proskey/Arena, 1998 April 20; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Embassy of Sweden, 1998 April 29; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Storytellers Evening, 1998 May 11; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Jazz Trio/Kenneth Carroll, 1998 May 12; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Spanish Dance, 1998 May 13; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Papermaking Workshop, 1998 May 16; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Richard Diebenkorn, 1998 May 19; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Stone Built, 1998 May 20; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Josephine, Bessie and Billie, 1998 May 26; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Pre-Raphaelite and Victorian Art, 1997 February 18; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SD Network TV, 1997 February 4; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Violins of Lafayette #3, 1997 February 2; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - James Wines: Green Architecture, 1997 January 29; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Current State of the Media #4 Bob Schieffer, 1997 February 3; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Current State of the Media #3, 1997 January 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Edith Wharton (Empty), 19997 January 27; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Attendance Payment, 1998 April - 1998 May; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Life Upon the Wicked Stage, 1997 February 15; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - MES Subscriptions 1, Circa 1998; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - MES Subscriptions 2, Circa 1998; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - MES Programming, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Tokyo, 1996 October 18; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The Eroica, 1996 November 15; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Ying, 1997 February 7; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Marcy Rosen, 1997 February 21; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Borromeo, 1997 March 21; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Takacs, 1997 April 11; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Marcy Rosen, 1997 May 2; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Brentano, 1997 May 23; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - MES Tickets, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Tony Gil, 1998 June 3; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Jenny Lind, 1998 June 8; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Octagon, 1998 June 9; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Manet, Monet The Gare St. Lazarre, 1998 June 15; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - David Rockwell, 1998 June 16; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - John Eaton, 1998 June 17; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Love Letters, 1998 June 22; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - A Great Day in Harlem, 1998 June 23; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Abandon, 1998 June 24; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - A Polish Nobleman, 1998 June 25; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Elle Decor, 1998 June 29; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Suburbs Under Siege, 1998 May 6; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - A Day With Ricasso, 1998 April 8; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Degas at the Races, 1998 May 18; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Corcoran March 1999 Public Programs Calendar, 1999 March; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - March 27 Fashion Seminar CANCELLED, 1999 March; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - S290 March 2,9,16 Peter Weir Film Series FY99, 1999 March 2,9,16; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - L278 March 15 Ruchard Brown FY99, 1999 March 15; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - L273 March 21 FY99 Environmental Film Festival, 1999 March 21; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Nest: A quarterly magazine of interiors Fall 1998, Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Ennvironmental Film Festival, 1999 March 18-28; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CGA Public Programs submitted to finance for payment, 1999; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Spring for the Corcoran! 1999, Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - L302 March 30 FY99 W. Brumfield Lecture, 1999 March 30; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - P235 April 5 FY99 Wooly Mammoth, 1999 April 5; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - L276 April 6 FY99 Ellington and his Music, 1999 April 6; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - P271 April 13 FY99 Jerry Rose, 1999 April 13; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - T299 April 14 FY99 16th Street Walking Tour, 1999 April 14; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - L288 April 14 FY99 S. Cash L. Robinson Lecture, 1999 April 14; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - P282 April 21 FY99 Dear Liar, 1999 April 21; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - L287 April 22 FY99 Frank Stella, 1999 April 22; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - L259 April 22 FY99 George Washington: Architect CANCELLED, 1999 April 22; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - L307 May 1 FY99 Eleanor: An American Love Story, 1999 May 1; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - CGA May Public Programs 1999, 1999 May; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - L297 May 11 FY99 Roderick Macleish CANCELLED, 1999 May 11; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - P283 May 4 FY99 John Eaton Concert, 1999 May 4; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - L301 May 5 FY99 Newseum: Andy Rooney w/ Ernie Pyle, 1999 May 5; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - L293 May 10 FY99 Maroon with a View, 1999 May 10; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Alfred A. Knopf folder, 1998; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - L296 May 12 FY99 Matisse Drives You Mad, 1999 May 12; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - SA295 May 19 FY99 Nordic Series: Sweden, 1999 May 19; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - L292 May 20 Leonard Oberlander FY99, 1999 May 20; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - L281 May 23 FY99 Printmaking Workshop, 1999 May 23; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - L272 May 27 FY99 The New American Garden, 1999 May 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Aspen Trip August 18-23, 1999, 1999 August 18-23; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - CGA June 1999 Public Programs Calendar, 1999 June; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - SB295 June 2 FY99 Nordic Series: Iceland, 1999 June 2; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - P284 June 3 Jenny Lind, 1999 June 3; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - L308 June 4 FY99 Mt. Vernon Gardens / Octagon, 1999 June 4; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - P285 June 6 FY99 Carol Lieberman Concert, 1999 June 6; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - L294 June 7 FY99 The History of American Illustration, 1999 June 7; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - SC295 June 9 FY99 Nordic Series: Finland, 1999 June 9; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - June 10 1999 Fashion Group, 1999 June 10; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - L298 June 12 FY99 Book-Making Workshop, 1999 June 12; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - P303 June 14 FY99 Satin Doll, 1999 June 14; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - T312 June 15 FY99 Embassy Row Walking Tour, 1999 June 15; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - L310 June 17 FY99 Roy Lichtenstein: Pop of the Line, 1999 June 17; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - P305 June 21 FY99 Hot Mustard, 1999 June 21; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - L304 June 22 FY99 Mary Cassatt, 1999 June 22; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - P311 June 23 FY99 Wild Fusion, 1999 June 23; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - P306 June 28 FY99 Judy Simmons, 1999 June 28; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - L309 June 30 FY99 Robert Lautman / Octagon, 1999 June 30; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - L214 July 7 FY99 Talk Back to the Critic, 1999 July 7; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - L209 July 13 FY99 Ragtime, 1999 July 13; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - P212 July 14 FY99 M. Spaulding Dance, 1999 July 14; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - S213 July 20 27 FY99 Whistler To Hopper, 1999 July 20,27; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - T232 July 29 FY99 Sequoia, 1999 July 29; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - L219 July 30 FY99 Carter Wiseman, 1999 July 30; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - August 1998 Calendar, 1998 August; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - P228 August 4 FY99 David McLaughlin Friends, 1999 August 4; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - P229 Auggust 10 FY99 Tribute to Sinatra CANCELLED, 1999 August 10; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - L222 August 11 FY99 An Evening in Africa, 1999 August 11; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - T225 August 5 FY99 Nicholas Alexandra Bus Tour, 1999 August 5; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - FR 1998-99 Season FY99 Washington Chamber Symphony, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - FR 1998-99 Season FY99 Contemporary Music Forum, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - P221 July 23 FY99 Mahina and The Polynesians CANCELLED, 1999 July 23; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - July 98 Cal, 1998 July; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - L208 July 1 FY99 Helen Frankenthaler, 1999 July 1; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Nicholas Alexandra: The Last Imperial Family of Tsarist Russia packet, 1998 August 1 - December 31; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - L233 August 6 FY99 45th Biennial, 1999 August 6; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - L223 August 13 FY99 Toulouse-Lautrec/I. McDonald, 1999 August 13; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - L238 August 20 FY99 Frankenthaler Cassatt Films, 1999 August 20; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - September 1998 Calendar - FY99 Public Programs, 199 September; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - September 23 FY99 Renaissance Revelers, 1999 September 23; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - September 23 FY99 Longwood Brandywine Tour, 1999 September 23; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - September 14 FY99 Embasssy of Ecuador, 1999 September 14; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Moore - The Power of Reservation Book 1998, Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - September 17 FY99 Arthur Cotten Moore, 1999 September 17; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - September 22 FYY99 Lucian Perkins, 1999 September 22; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - September 26 FY99 Women Fashion Designers, 1999 September 26; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Neiman Marcus thebook Oct. 1998, 1998 October; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - September 28 FY99 Yawari, 1999 September 28; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - October 1998 Calendar FY99 Public Programs, 1998 October; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Anders Widmark Trio 10/1 P240, 1998 October 1; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - October 5 FY99 Goethe - Brecht, 1999 October 5; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Contemp. Music 5/6 10/8, 2/2, 1999; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - S239 October 13, 19, 21, 26 Architecture in Embassies FY99, 1999 October; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - L237 October 14 FY99 In Praise of Americans Collectors, 1999 October 14; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - October 15 FY99 Molly Smith, 1999 October 15; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - P227 Oct. 18, Nov. 22, Mar. 7 May 2 / Violins of Lafayette, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Violins of Lafayette: 3/7/99, 1999 March 7; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - NC Wyeth/David Michaelis, 1999 October 20; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Psychoanalytic Film Series, 1999 October - 1999 November; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - S. American Concert Series, 1999 October; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1998 Calendar Public Programming, 1998 November; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Belgian Evening Cancelled, 1999 November 20; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Screaming Woman Next, 1999 November 2; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Eric Denker, 1999 November - 1999 December; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Book-Making Workshop, 1999 November 7; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sunny Sumter, 1999 November 9; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Embassy of Israel, 1999 November 15; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jackson Pollock, 1999 November 16; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - David Adamasko, 1999 November 18; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Steve Ross, 1999 November 23; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Decemebr 1998 Calendar Public Programs, 1998 December; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Frank Loch - Cancelled, 1999 December 9; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Octogon, 1999 December 2; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Delacroix, 1999 December 14; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Delacroix Bus Tour, 1999 December 15; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newseum, 1999 December 17; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Calendar January 1999, 1999 January; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Germany Cancelled, 1999 January 28; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Thomas Folk, 1999 January 19; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Ziva's Spanish Dance Ensemble, 1999 January 20; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - George Sexton, 1999 January 21; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Little Known Museums in Around Paris, 1999 January 26; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Susan Nigra Snyder, 1999 January 27; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - NY Designers, Circa 1999; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Art Directors Club of Met. Washington, 1999 February 28; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - John Beardsley, 1999 February 18; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Peter Vaughn, 1999 February 1; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Charles Hoberrman, 1999 February 2; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Theater Panel, 1999 February 8; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Joseph Holtzman, 1999 Febrruary 9; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Parthenon Symposium, 1999 February 13; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Larry Willis Trio, 1999 February 21; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Illustrators Series, 1999 February - 1999 May; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - John Singer Sargetn, 1999 February 25; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Moonfire, 1999 February 28; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Playwrights Series II, 1999 February - 1999 March; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - July Calendar / disc for JWS, 1999 July; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - July 26 FY2000 Winners Concert, 2000 July 26; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - July 1 FY2000 Swiss Evening: Paul Giger, 2000 Julyy 1; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - July 7 FY2000 Portraits By Ingres: Images, 2000 July 7; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - L312 July 8 FY2000 The Sixties: Pop And Content, 2000 July 8; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - July 9 FY2000 Bill Warrell, 2000 July 9; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - July 13 FY2000 Love Letters, 2000 July 13; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - July 14 FY2000 Jaymie Meyer, 2000 July 14; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - July 19 FY2000 Lee Roy Reams Concerts, 2000 July 19; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - July 22,29, August 5 FY2000 Stanley Kubrick Film Series, 2000 July-August; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - August 9 FY2000 Gandhara, 2000 August 9; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Calendar FY2000 September Copy, Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - September 7 FY2000 Rememberence to Proust Chopin, 2000 September 77; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Nouvelles Images 1998, Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - September 9 FY2000 Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 2000 September 9; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ibero-American Concert Series FY2000, Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - September 13 FY2000 Diane Sommerfield, 2000 September 13; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - September 21 FY2000 Steve Ross, 2000 September 21; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - P305A September 23 FY2000 Ibero-American Concert Series #1, 2000 September 23; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - September 28 FY2000 Portuguese Series #1, 2000 September 28; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - September 29 FY2000 J. Perna, 2000 September 29; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 99 Oct PP Cal FY2000, 1999 October; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - October 4 FY2000 on site at the Corcoran, 2000 October 4; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - October 6 FY2000 A Couple of Blaguards, 2000 October 6; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - October 20 FY2000 Haunting The Movies, 2000 October 20; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - October 26 FY2000 Portuguese Series #3, 2000 October 26; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - October 14 FY2000 Ibero-American Concert Series #2, 2000 October 14; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - October 17 FY2000 Sam Harry's Tastings / Talk, 2000 October 17; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sam and Harrys, Circa 2000; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - October 18 FY2000 Laurie Olin Evening, 2000 October 18; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - October 19 FY2000 Nick Olcott, 2000 October 19; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - October 22 FY2000 Lithuanian Embassy, 2000 October 22; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - October 25 FY2000 Michael Guerin, 2000 October 25; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - October 12 FY2000 Portuguese Series #2, 2000 Octobber 12; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - T342 October 28 FY2000 NY Fashion Trip, 2000 October 28; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - November Public Programs Calendar, 1999 November; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - An Evening of Venezuela Cancelled, 2000 November 18; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Klaas Hofstra Cancelled, 2000 November 14; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ivan Karp Lecture Cancelled, 2000 November 22; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Helen Kornblum, 2000 November 1; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Ibero-American Concert Series #3, 2000 November 4; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - OAS, Red Cross, CGA Tour, 2000 November 5; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Sam Harry's Tastings/Talk, 2000 November 7; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - John Eaton Concert, 2000 November 9; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dazzling Interiors, 2000 November 10; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Slovakian Cultural Evening, 2000 November 15; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Woolly Mammoth, 2000 November 29; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - The Master Forger, 2000 November 30; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 1999 December Public Programing Calendar, 2000 December; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Chinese Art at it's Best Cancelled, 2000 December 15; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Tony Gil and Charlie Byrd Cancelled, 2000 December 8; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Decorating for the Holidays Cancelled, 2000 December; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Marty Henne, 2000 Decemebr 2; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ziva's Spanish Dance, 2000 December 5; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Whitehaven Walking Tour, 2000 December 7; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Ibero-American Concert Series #4, 2000 December 9; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Evening at Ecuador, 2000 December 13; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hand Bells Performance, 2000 December 14; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - October 1999 Attendance, 1999 October 13 - 1999 October 28; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - October 29 - November 15, 1999 Attendance, 1999 October 29 - 1999 November 15; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - November 1999 Attendance, 1999 November 16 - 1999 November 30; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - December 1999 Attendance, 1999 December 2 - 1999 December 9; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - January 2000 Attendance, 2000 January 3 - 2000 January 31; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - February 2000 Attendance, 2000 February 2 - 2000 February 28; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - March 1 - April 2, 2000 Attendance, 2000 March 1 - 2000 April 2; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - April 2000 Attendance, 2000 April; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - May 2000 Attendance, 2000 May; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - June 2000 Attendance, 2000 June; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - July 2000 Attendance, 2000 July; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - August 2000 Attendance, 2000 August; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - September 2000 Attendane, 2000 September; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - October 2000 Attendance, 2000 October; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - November-December 2000 Attendance, 2000 November - 2000 December; Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - January 2000 Public Program Calendar, 2000 Januar; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Moonlighters Cancelled, 2000 January 12; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Imaginary Invalid Cancelled, 2000 January 27; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Great Magazines, Great Photography Cancelled, 2000 January 26; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - A Conversation with Herbblock, 2000 January 10; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Vicarious Tour of Washington Architecture, 2000 January 13; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Leonard Slatkin, 2000 January 19; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Luxembourg Off Site, 2000 January 31; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - February 2000 Public Program Calendar, 2000 February; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Dick Stolley (Life) Cancelled, 2000 February 8; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - The Only Way to Cross Cancelled, 2000 February 23; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Bernard Tschumi, 2000 February 29; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Congressman Symington, 2000 February 2; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - A Bacchanalian History of Wine, 2000 February 10; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Phyllis Richman, 2000 February 15; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sybil, Circa 2000; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Black Gal Needin' to be Loved, 2000 February; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Ibero-American Concert Series #6, 2000 February 17; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Topkapi: The Movie, 2000 February 20; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - President's Council, 2000 February 21; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Elle Editor Talk, 2000 February 22; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Rachel Kaplan, 2000 February 24; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Coolidge Quartet, 2000 February 27; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Neiman Marcus/Fashion Group, 2000 February 28; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - March 2000 Public Program Calendar, 2000 March; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Playwrights #1, 2000 March 1; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Playwrights, 2000 March 8; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Playwright Series, 2000 March; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Playwrights, 2000 April 24; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Yale Alley Cats Cancelled, 2000 March 9; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Ibero-America Concert Series #6 Cancelled, 2000 March 30; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Playwrights, 2000 March 15; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Film Director's Series, 2000 February - 2000 March; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - David Levy on David Smith, 2000 March 21; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 34)